The future of humanity is in her hands.
Atlas is a science fiction, action film directed by Brad Peyton.
A brilliant counterterrorism analyst with a deep distrust of AI discovers it might be
her only hope when a mission to capture a renegade robot goes awry.
Atlas Shepherd, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Harlan Shepherd, played by Simu Liu.
Colonel Elias Banks, played by Sterling K. Brown.
Smith (voice) / Dhiib Pilot, played by Gregory James Cohan.
Casca Decius, played by Abraham Popoola.
Val Shepherd, played by Lana Parrilla.
Atlas is a 2024 American science fiction action film starring Jennifer Lopez as a skilled counterterrorism analyst, who harbors a profound distrust of artificial
intelligence, and who comes to realize that it may be her sole recourse following the failure of a mission aimed at apprehending a rogue robot.
The film is directed by Brad Peyton and written by
Leo Sardarian and Aron Eli Coleite.
The film also stars Simu Liu, Sterling K.
Brown, and Mark Strong.
A co-production of ASAP Entertainment, Safehouse Pictures, Nuyorican Productions and
Berlanti-Schechter Films, Atlas was released by Netflix on May 24, 2024.
It was negatively received by critics, but was successful on Netflix, reaching the
platform's Top 10 list in 93 countries, including the number one spot in 71 of them.
The film explores themes of mission, artificial
intelligence (a.i.), exploration, attack, soldier.
The tone is thought_provoking.